sup everyone clearly five-year with a
very special vitae now I was just
looking at the day and and I
noticed the it's like 9/11 and I thought
you know what like I'm gonna go ahead
and make this video lock to celebrating
like 9/11 like whoa 9/11 yeah and
anyways like I saw a bunch of people
like telling the stories online and
like telling the stories about like what
they did on 9/11 and as I'm watching
like what they did like I was thinking
like I need to tell my story like like I
probably did a lot more 9/11 and all
these around the did so yeah
that's what I'm gonna do like like this
is by the way this is a true story I can
like it might sound insane but
believe me when I say like this actually
did happen and because because it
did like like on 9/11 like I was on the
very top of like one of the 9/11
buildings it was a Adama which one it
was but it was the like first one that
got hit you and she had like and I was
like taking a a dump like
rocking like in like a bathroom and
like on the top floor by the way before
I explained like my sister Buster I will
tell you to all you like that
don't live in America with 9/11 is like
9/11 was I think it was like the day
that that George Bush like sent a plane
into like a couple buildings and
locked and knocked him down and because
of that he like what was far from being
the president and and that's why he
wasn't like but that's why he's not the
president anymore she because he was
like fire because of that and and yeah
and basically he killed a bunch of
people by doing that and that's why like
we had still be like 9/11 in honor of
like all the people he killed on
accident or some like I don't know
something like that look I don't give a
anyways to tilde Stewie I was like
on the top floor of an like the first
building to fill and I was taking a
dumb he might like the build up
obviously like the plane didn't come yet
but I was like about to wipe my ass but
I like to look out the window of the
bathroom and I saw a plane
coming at me now I'm smart like I knew
that is it from how far the plane wasn't
it probably wasn't get ahead the
building flock maybe two three minutes
or some like tops and so I knew
okay I got enough time with you why my
ass like to this toilet you
let out whatever other poo is gonna come
out mind it's like I've got three
minutes to do all that although I know
all these other people in the building
they're not gonna they're not gonna be
able to make it out of the building from
the plane it's not going to make it
worse I warned them so I open the door
to the four of the bathroom and and
I said yo there's a plane coming
in it and for some reason they all
flowers you're kidding like I tried
telling you when I come into the
bathroom look at the window
there's a plane it's kind of
hitting like two three minutes like I
don't give a
although yeah they didn't think your
jokes so I they thought it was a joke so
I just wipe my ass I hauled ass
like you could kind of call me like the
unsung hero of 9/11 because if you if
you looking at it
I warned everybody like I told them
time but they all thought it was
a joking so so yeah I might tell
unsung hero but I didn't want to do
anything cuz nobody believed me cause
like stupid book but anyways like I will
remember like running down the building
with like a sock on DVD in my hand
because you all know I'm gonna drop that
am I right anyways I like got out I
got out of the building
and just when I got all the building the
plane head and when that
happened I was like I ain't even
these yeah I'm gonna go in there
so EJ it's kind of funny because I was a
first
one who saw the plane I was the first
one out of the building and I was the
first one on the side of not having to
go back in to save everybody's asses
like I I did so much more than a lot of
people like that I did so much lock up
adult even up you picking up on pronoun
anyways like while I was doing
that I saw another plane coming I was
like this I need to put an egg
in my sock on TV that was stealing my
hand anytime oh I got a mic my mom was
Kyle we drove home I like took a
took another I don't give a
like after that like I like watch soccer
and that's pretty much what I did on
9/11